# CHRISTINA XAMIN

#### CONTACT

cxamin@gmail.com



(416)-523-3132



www.christinaxamin.com

Oakville, ON, Canada

### SKILLS

- Proficient in Adobe Creative Suite
- Excels using prototyping software including Adobe XD, Sketch and InVision
- Understanding of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Team player with excellent communication skills
- Able to make decisions and work through problems
- Manages time effectively
- · Easily adapts to new situations
- Presents ideas and opinions in an open and unbiased way
- Comfortable engaging with stakeholders to gather data and requirements
- Translates requirements into research needs. prototypes and testing
- Able to map user journey through to final stage

Ambitious UI/UX designer with 3+ years experience in a professional design environment and a Bachelor of Interaction Design degree. Additional 4 years of academic design experience at Sheridan College. Background in visual and creative arts. Excellent communication skills.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Interaction Design Sheridan College**

September 2014 - April 2018

# **Visual and Creative Arts Advanced Diploma Sheridan College**

January 2012 - May 2014

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER** Surrey Place, Toronto, ON

August 2018- Present

- Interviewed stakeholders (including partners and end users) to gather and determine requirements
- Developed wireframes and prototypes based on user research then organized usability testing for project development
- Lead user testing sessions, analyzed findings and provided design updates and recommendations to further project progress

# INTERACTIVE AND TECHNICAL MEDIA WRITER INTERN Rapid7, Toronto, ON

May 2017- September 2017

- Guided users through UI by contributing to company's software help documentation
- Collaborated with multiple teams to create documents that outlined in-product features

## **GRAPHIC DESIGN ASSISTANT (CONTRACT)** Oakville Public Library, Oakville, ON

May 2016- August 2016

- Created various promotional material for print, web and environmental applications
- Maintained a graphic consistency by adhering to the library's visual identity and AODA compliancy